Mom needs a little space.
Mars Needs Moms is a adventure, animation, family film directed by Simon Wells.
When Martians suddenly abduct his mom, mischievous Milo rushes to
the rescue and discovers why all moms are so special.
Milo (performance capture), played by Seth Green.
Milo (voice) (as Seth Dusky), played by Seth Robert Dusky.
Mom (voice), played by Joan Cusack.
Gribble (voice), played by Dan Fogler.
Alien (voice), played by Breckin Meyer.
Ki (voice), played by Elisabeth Harnois.
Mars Needs Moms is a 2011 American animated science fiction
comedy film, co-written and directed by Simon Wells.
Based on the Berkeley Breathed book, the film was animated through the process of performance capture
and stars Seth Green, Dan Fogler, Elisabeth Harnois, Mindy Sterling, and Joan Cusack.
It tells the story of a nine-year-old boy named Milo who sets out to
save his mother on Mars after she is abducted by Martians.
Mars Needs Moms premiered at the El Capitan Theatre in Los Angeles on March 6, 2011,
and was released in theaters on March 11, 2011 by Walt Disney Pictures.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and was a box-office bomb, grossing $39 million
on a $150 million budget, and losing an estimated $100–144 million for Disney.
The film explores themes of rescue, alien, martian,
alien abduction, alien invasion.